

Courtney Jones

Professional Summary

Certified and motivated developer, with 3+ years engineering field experience, 2+ years experience in front-end developing. Extremely comfortable working with ReactJS, in javascript and typescript. With a foundation in quality assurance, and great interpersonal skills.

Work History

Reliant Immune Diagnositcs - Front-End Web Developer

Austin, TX

09/2020 - Current

- Collaborated with designers and back-end developers to plan new features based on stakeholders needs.
- Built UI for customer facing and in-house admin web applications, connected these UI's to internal and external API's.
- Developed, tested, and shipped new features. Addressed bugs and feature enhancements in fast paced start up environment.
- Independently created mocks and planned features adhering to branding standards during high volume times.

Reliant Immune Diagnostics - QA Engineer

Austin, TX

01/2019 - 06/2020

- Developed and maintained automated and manual regression test suits using Cypress and Practitest software.
- Organized and Executed 20+ end user and 10+ beta testing events. Along with Guerrilla Usability testing on 50+ test subjects.
- Provided technical information in change request meetings with company stakeholders.
- Escalated concerns about new and existing features during development cycles.

Reliant Immune Diagnostics: MDBox - Lead Lab Tech

Austin, TX

10/2017 - 01/2019

- Wrote protocol documents for 10+ FDA Validation studies.
- Served as member of study teams and provided analytical support to justify clinical trial design and ongoing analysis during protocol

✓ courtneyrjones95@gmail.com

7373461265

Q Austin, TX 78729

Profiles

• Github: CRJones

• LinkedIn: courtney-jones-458362b3/

Skills

- ReactJS
- Javascript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS (SASS)
- Bootstrap
- Git/Github
- Docker
- Cypress
- Practitest
- Bugsnag
- Visual Studio Code
- Figma
- Jira and Confluence

Education

09/2020

University of Texas At Austin

Austin, TX

Certificate: Full-Stack Development

12/2017

development.

- Performed 10+ rigorous data collection studies for FDA approval application, using R and in-house software.
- Trained and supervised 30+ lab interns.

Concordia University At Austin

Austin, TX

Bachelor of Science: Biology